Well, it's started, Upcami. This time we have with us Shiori Nishida of Beyond Subway and Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。 24.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you our recording, rehearsal and other production processes.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs. I, Nishida, would like to talk about the Hello Project concert in winter,
We have a rehearsal every time to check the sound before the show. During the rehearsal, when we were playing Beyonds's song, the other group members were really excited in the audience.
They get really excited.
It makes me very happy, and also Haruka Inoue from Morning Musume。 14's Haruka Inoue and Akko Yumeguita's growth because we are touring together,
I'm very happy to be able to see their growth. It's been a lot of fun.
It's something that only Halocon can do. It's really great to be able to tour together with other groups. It will be interesting if we don't start from now on, but I don't mean growing together,
I hope we can continue to improve the music we perform together.
And I, Sakurai, will be in the year 2024, and I will be called "Morning Musume。 23 to '24.
We, Morning Musume。 Every time a new year begins, the number of the year after Morning Musume。 The number of the year after "Morning Musume,
Just at that time, Morning Musume。 The number of the year was 1,4, so it's been 10 whole years.
Wow!
Yes, this year has passed.
When the number changed from 2,2 to 2,3, I felt that it would take some time to get used to it,
But after 1 and 4, I felt that I would be able to get used to 2 and 4,
But I'm sure...
In the beginning, I was like, "Morning Musume。 I'm sure that in the beginning, I'll be like, "Toots! I'm sure that in the beginning, I'll be like, "Thank you, Morning Musume。That's right.
I feel that the year has begun. I really appreciate Morning Musume。 You always say very important greetings at the beginning of the year and at the end of the year.
I really feel that it is the end of the year or the beginning of the year because it is the time of change.
I am really looking forward to the next year's 2.5.
Let's start with this year's up-date.
Making of the making of the music video for "Ochanoma Good Luck's Heartache
Here is the making of the music video for the song "Good Luck's Bust" from Ochanoma's latest album, released on January 10.
It's like all kinds of fans come here.
Why is the store where it originated just the right place?
It's just the right line.
So it's like we're going to point them out one at a time.
You know what?
There's a place where we have to run.
It's a little bit slippery here.
So I had to grit my teeth while running.
That's probably what you're seeing in the film.
La La La La La...
The first time I told you, my dear ones.
Don't make fun of me for dreaming too big.
Thank you for listening to me with a serious face. Thank you for listening with such a serious face.
And that's when our hearts began to resonate.
I'll never have a chance if I just wait and see
All over the country, one by one, until I make this song echo...
It's us, it's me, from the water to the sea
We used to shoot a lot of dance scenes and other scenes that were divided into various parts,
But we don't get to do it like this, in a single cut,
So I think it's very difficult to make the equipment and the techniques so that the camera can't see them, but I'm having a lot of fun.
I am very happy. I will do my best.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to be able to shoot with a ganter-ganter.
It is difficult to shoot an acting music video because when I started, I focused on dancing and singing,
And this time, we are going to shoot uncut, so I am struggling a lot because I have to keep connecting one by one,
I'm hoping that we can make a good music video.
I'm hoping that we can make a good music video,
The smaller and backward you are, the better you can shoot with the camera.
Naleigh and arms
ㆵっとして.
Aragi.
Then, right-right-kun get
let's go get this area.
Thank you for watching.
I'm the one who wants
More.
Camera's rolling.
Okay, we'll play it.
Come on, please.
It's the first time I'm getting it right.
The timing is all over the place.
Innocent personalities
clashed with each other.
Still, it's fun
Every day is new
Exciting and exciting
An unexpected marriage
There must be someone waiting for us somewhere in the world
I'll make your skin and your tea-posts stand up, with my singing voice
Thank you for your hard work! Thanks for your hard work!
Yes, OK.
Here's the next cutscene
Thank you for watching!
I'm going to put my hand like this.
And then, you know, you see one person, and then they all show up, and then their outfits change.
It's like the whole scene changes at once.
I want you to move your hands like this.
And it doesn't start.
It doesn't start.
It stops pretty soon, doesn't it?
It's better if it doesn't start.
Okay, I've turned it around. Please.
One, two, three, four, two, two, three, four, three, three, four, two, three, four.
Watch your heads, everybody. Watch your heads, watch your heads. Don't fall off.
Yes, let's start running.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,  Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
♪ One of my own ♪
Hold me, I'm not crying now
I didn't move!
Ok.
I was so embarrassed.
It was the kind of scene where acting skill is important.
I thought a lot about what kind of expression I should make.
I don't know how it went.
I don't know until I see the finished product.
But I did my best in my own way.
I did my best.
I hope a lot of people will see this music video.
Yes! We just finished shooting a music video called "Good Luck's Heartache"!
Okay, let's see...
It was a very long but short shoot today.
It's a short music video, but you can see the personalities and faces of the members in it.
I think it's a music video where you can see the personalities of the members and their true faces in this short music video.
And there is one highlight.
I, Tsukishiki, used to play basketball.
I used to play basketball, and today was the first time I played basketball in a music video. I played basketball for the first time today, probably on the set of a music video.
Last time...
In the song "Emotionally Unstable"...
I had touched the ball a little bit, but...
But this is the first time for me to really shoot a ball.
I've never really shot a ball before.
I hope you will pay attention to it!
Please watch it!
This music video was shot in one shot, so we had to run and move when the camera wasn't on, and then get caught on camera.
It must have been hard work for the members, and also for the cameraman to cooperate with them. It looked like a lot of work!
If the timing was a little off, they would be caught in places they shouldn't be, so I imagined it was a very nerve-wracking shoot.
But everyone seemed to be having a great time, and the smiles were so natural that only a single shot could do, and the visuals were so cute!
I really want to look back at them over and over again. I thought it was a music video that made me want to fall in love with all of them.
The song itself and the dance moves are very eye-catching. I thought it was a song that would stay in your ears and the choreography was easy to remember, so I hope you will dance to it on TikTok or something.
I would love to dance to it on TikTok or something like that. I thought the choreography was something that many people could dance along with.
It was really wonderful.I am sure we will see more performances in the future, so I am really looking forward to it!
This is the making of "Ocha-no-Ma: Good Luck's Chest Thumping" music video shooting.
Ocha no Oma! 1st album Channel 1 is now on sale!
Thanks for all your hard work!
Next, here it is!
Morning Musume。' 23 Wake Up Call Wake Up When You Wake Up Dance Lesson
Morning Musume。' 23's latest single
Please take a look at the dance lesson for "Wake Up Call: When I Wake Up.
At first, when you put this hand out from under you, you have to start a little bit lower than you are.
Seven, eight, one, two, three, four, five.
Five, six, seven, eight, and then three, four.
You don't have to think of it as that at all.
It's more like, "Let me show myself." Three, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
And here, a little more persistence. 1,2,3,4,5,6,7.
The next one you open is not an image, it's what you pull out.
Five, six, seven, eight.
That kind of makeup doesn't suit you. It forces a femininity that can't be erased.
Most of the time, it's not for you. That's all I'm saying.
Keep your hands to yourself.
It's important now. Cut off your hand.
I don't know.
You can get out.You can leave.
Yes, sir. Sorry.
That's all I have to say.
Just put your face back for a second. I'll take two slow ones.
Yes, sir.
That's all I have to say.
Just for you.
I just did a lousy job of it, and now...
We're almost there.
I'm just gonna go over there and drop off a bottle or two.
You sure?
You don't look good in that makeup. It puts on an air of femininity that you can't get rid of.
I'm not doing it for you, that's all I'm saying.
I'm just trying to say... pretty, pretty girl, little girl, little girl, little girl.
A creature with a woman's nature, a girl who loves and loves more.
You have to love a girl more, a creature with a woman's nature.
I'm sure it's a bore when they do it to you.
I can't sleep with those eyes of my dreams. I can't sleep.
I'm sad
I'm your girl
We don't call When I wake up
It's time to enjoy life
The sun is in my heart
Just do it, just do it, just do it, just do it
Your heart is a fireball
Summer in the morning, someone's heart I'll light it up
Let me dance, let me dance, let me dance, let me dance
Sweets, that back lip is so good, it's amazing
One more time
Even now, you're in the silhouette center.
You know,
At the yolk.
They both sing, you know, morning, evening, morning.
At least in the yole.
Seino, yes.
There at night
When the fading calories
I'll jack me to the wind I'm gonna jack me to the wind
Dance baby, dance baby, dance baby, dance baby, dance
Jack me to the wind
Don't tell me it's boring
I don't care if you're not ready
Don't you care about me
I wish everyone would be a little more varied in this "What a bore!" part.
Yes, I do.
So,
At this point in time..,
I felt like everyone was really backing down at this point.
Yes, Kanmiri.
Yes.
Se-no,
Thank you very much.
Can I give a "hoo"?
Se-no,
Uh, that's okay.
It's fine like that.
Let's just let it flow a little bit.
[ED]
Thank you for your time.
All I want to do is live vicariously through you.
Time can always hurt.
You and you are the fun
I love you so much that I'll take my fame and drink my breath away
Cause I know what every face really looks like
I bet it sucks to leave it up to someone else
I want to live for you 'cause that's all I want to do
Time can always be a pain
And you and you are the fun ones
Cause I love you and I'll take my fame and I'll take my breath away
Cause I know what every face really looks like
It must be so boring to leave it up to others
I'll decide for myself what I want and what I don't want
I don't want you to cheat me
Wake up! Story It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
The sun pads are in control
Just do it, Just do it, Just do it, Just do it
Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance
I can't see myself as far as the bread can take me
I can't realize my life experience alone
People are the best
You can't realize this if you give up
Yes, this new song is a song with two new members.
So this song is about how the 14 member lineup is going to look like from now on.
I wanted to make it a cheerful song that makes you imagine how the 14-member lineup is going to look like from now on.
It's energetic, but everyone tries to make it sound like it's going to be perfect.
So I tried not to put too much emphasis on that concept.
It's my personal concept.
Call is a fun song with a lot of energy, so I think we should have fun dancing to it.
Call is a fun song with a great rhythm, so I think I have to enjoy dancing to it.
I'm still not very good at dancing, so I haven't been able to get through it completely.
I don't think I can enjoy it to the fullest.
I'm going to practice more so that I can do the choreography without having to think
I want to practice more.
I want to practice more so that I can enjoy the dance as much as I can without thinking about it.
The point I want you to pay attention to in the choreography of "Wake up!
There is my rap part.
I come out to the center of the stage and point at the audience like this.
I want you to pay attention to that.
Yes, Wake Up Call, I'm sure some of you know this song, but it has lyrics of past songs of Morning Musume。 Some of you may know that this song contains lyrics, titles, and song titles from past Morning Musume。
The Peace, Congratulations, Revolution, etc. are included in this song, and the song features not only the lyrics but also the choreography of "The Peace," which we all do together. I think this song is unique in that it pays homage to The Peace.
My personal favorite part of the choreography of this song, and the key point of the choreography, is when it enters the B-melody.
The key point of the choreography is in the B-melody, where the choreographer says, "It would be boring to leave it to others if we don't affirm it.
Down! Then they all come together in the middle of the song and wave and accentuate it like this. I like it.
I like that part. The teacher gave us a lot of advice that he wanted to show how the dancers were moving like a wave.
When we go on tour together, we should try to keep the energy of the original as much as possible.
I think this is the point that I still try to keep the energy of the original and dance as tightly as possible.
We had this dance lesson in the summer. It was last summer. When I realized it, quite a few months had passed.
Haruka Inoue and Ako-chan, who ran away, are now members of the 17th term and this single is their review single.
I'm also very happy, and I think I've been able to have a little bit of leeway with them since they joined less than a year after I joined the group.
I'm very happy because I feel like I'm growing with them.I feel that we are growing together and I am very happy about that.
Is this your second single? Yes, this is my second single.
I realized that Rio Sakurai is my senior.
The two members of the 17th term are heels.
We also had hi-tech dance lessons, and dancing in heels is not something you can just ask them to do,
So I felt that the practice has made us what we are today,
This song is really cool to see live, isn't it?
I really like this song, so I hope everyone will see it at the live performance.
That's all for now. 23, Wake up call! It was a dance lesson for waking up.
You're working hard, you're cool!
Beyonds, Shiori Nishida from Subway and Rio Sakurai from Morning Musume。 24, Rio Sakurai, is sending you up-cam.
Here's the next one!
Angerme Red Line Vocal Recording
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Redline Kamisharyo Moe from Angerme's latest single!
Okay, let's take some pictures, shall we?
Yes, please.
Okay, first of all, four seconds of AML.
Okay, let's go back to the place I want to go home.
Yes, please.
I wonder if I'm allowed to be an idiot.
I'm taking the moon bus. I just want to go home.Okay.
Yes, well, the nuance is perfect for the fourth one, too.
I'm going to Hase too.
Hase, a place to get in the groove.
I wonder if I'm allowed to be an idiot.
I'll be on the bus in May. I want to go home.
Okay.
Tat-tat-tat-tat-tat-tat-tat-tat-tat-tat.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes...
Let's go.
Let's go
Yes, sir.
I wonder if I'm allowed to be an idiot... cyanide everywhere
I'll be on the next bus. I just want to go home.
I want to go home. Okay. - Okay.
Okay, yes.
Okay. Next location.
I missed you so much. I really missed you. I don't know if it's true. I'm in the middle of a database.
I'm almost glad you're here, but I'm not sure.
Almost... but not quite...
Yes, ma'am.
I've missed you so much.
One for each of you, please.
Yes, ma'am.
I missed you so much. I really missed you.
I don't think so.
I'm not being honest. I'm unconsciously requesting...
Adjusting the tone when singing the lyrics
I think we're connecting a bit now.
Yes, I'm here.
Just a little bit of time.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay?
Yes, please.
I'm not sure I'll be able to do it... if I don't qualify.
I've had a long time to think about it, and I've worked it out.
Today's itinerary.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
You can go to the next rap.
Or you can just say you want to get ripped off.
Oh, you want to go to the wrap.
Yes, sir.
Today's itinerary is the one I've been worrying about.
I'm gonna say it's for you
Yes, this area is OK
Yes, I'm gonna say
Let's start with the torn cousin
Yes, sir. Yes, ma'am.
You look at me like you love me, but tell me how you really feel.
How does a torn heart feel?
How does it feel to have pain that you've forgotten?
Yes, OK
Yes, sir.
Okay, now let's go to the end.
The first chorus
Yes, sir.
I'm gonna say it's for you
Cross the Red Line I want to get hurt, hurt, hurt
I do I do I break the levee of love
Red Line This kiss is proof that I'm ready
I do I do I do I'll only show you Red Line
I do I do it like that
Red Line
Red Line I want to hurt you
I do I do
This kiss, Red Lass, this kiss is a girly moment
I do, I do
From I do I do onward is the lyrics now.
Yes, I do, I do, I do
OK.
Let's go.
Please do.
Okay, I guess that's it then. I guess that's all then.
Thank you very much.
I really love Angstrom's Redline.
I have watched the music video many times since it was released,
Now that I've seen the recording, I can see how the rhythm of the singing was filmed,
I was able to understand how the singers were told to take a little space in between each verse,
By listening to the recording, I was able to understand what he was doing, though it is not a correct answer,
I think that by listening to the recording video, I was able to understand that,
I think that the recording videos are very important for me, as an idol, Recording videos are a great way for me, as an idol, to learn a lot,
I learned a lot from the recording videos,
I thought that Appeals Ryo's straight singing voice and facial expression were what I really liked.
It is already stuck in my head. It was so beautiful.
Appel's voice is so easy to understand the lyrics, and her tongue is so smooth that the lyrics just come right in.
I really love her voice, and her small face makes the headphones look big, so I felt again that she is a beautiful woman when I saw her backside.
This was the vocal recording of Moe Appellate Dormitory of Angerme Redline.
Angerme Redline
Thank you.
It's time to say goodbye to Upokami, brought to you by Shiori Ishida and Rio Sakurai.
We've seen a lot of different videos this time, but for me, Sakurai, the music video shooting of Ocha no Oma-san's Good Luck's Chest Thumping left a deep impression.
Music video shoots are often done from morning till night in a very tight schedule, but I was very impressed with the music video shoots of various groups.
I love watching the making of music video shoots of various groups.
I like to watch the making of music videos of various groups and discover new things such as how the set was set up, or how the lip scene was shot with this kind of lighting.
I don't know...
I think that music videos create a worldview that is unique to the song, so I'm really looking forward to shooting more music videos of Morning Musume.
I'm sure Morning Musume。 I'm sure they will release music videos in the future, so please look forward to it!
Yes, I, Nishida, saw the video of Morning Musume。 2 and 3's dance lesson when they were waking up from the wake-up call.
I would like to see more growth of Morning Musume。
Personally, I really liked Rio Sakurai's part at the bottom of the night in the last chorus.
I think it fits her voice so well and it's so cool to hear it live.
I'd like to keep an eye on her at live performances.
Thank you very much.
In this episode of up-cam, we'll be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Up-Front Group, and we'll be showing you things you don't normally see.
This time, UpCami is joined by Shiori Nishida from BEYONES Subway and Rio Sakurai from Morning Musume。 24's Rio Sakurai.
Good bye.
Next time on Upokami
Angerme: Life is Beautiful Dance Lesson
And
Juice-Juice Wonderful World 2023 Juice- Juice Ver.
Enjoy!
Please subscribe to our channel!